incryptoview.info 2019-06-23

# Privacy policy – InCryptoView.info

### **Who we are.**

On our site [incryptoview.info](https://incryptoview.info/) you can express your opinion and find out the opinion of other people on the market by voting. Also, you can look at the market and watch the trend.

### **Usage Statistics.**

We use Google Analytics and Metrika Yandex.

### **Social Media.**

We use Twitter.

### **What personal data we collect and why we collect it.**

We collect information about cookies for comfortable and convenient use of the site, also, during registration you will be asked to use your email address, name and gender (may also information about yourself for profile interest)

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience.  Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
  * To improve our website.  We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you
  * To improve customer services.  Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs

The email address from which you send the question, suggestions or the like may be used to send you information and updates.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or transferred to any other company for any reason, without your consent, except for law enforcement for violation of the law.

### **Cookie.**

We use cookies for your convenience. We store cookies for 1 year.

Popup Maker: We use anonymous cookies to prevent users from seeing the same popup repetitively in an attempt to make our users experience more pleasant while still delivering time sensitive messaging.

Cookies are small files of a service type with textual information that are stored in a computer’s browser. They contain certain data of the sites you visit. The simplest example of how cookies work is memorizing your account credentials on various sites.

### **Embedded content from other websites.**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content.

### **Who we share your data with.**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### **What do we use your data for.**

Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site.

### **Links to third parties.**

Sometimes, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. Therefore, we are not responsible for the content and activities of these sites. However, we strive to protect the integrity of our site.

### **How long we retain your data.**

We store cookies 1 year for more convenient use with the site.

### **Contact information.**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us. Our mail: hello@incryptoview.info

Turning to this mail, please, select the desired site (InCryptoView or ViewFaucet).

When you contact by mail, your data will not be transferred to third parties. In the case of an illegal message, we are entitled to contact law enforcement agencies.

### **How we protect your data.**

We use Let’s Encrypt certificate and 2FA.

### **What are the procedures against data hacking.**

We use strong protection to enter the admin panel.

### **Provide data.**

The data presented on the incryptoview.info website are for informational purposes only and are not intended for use in transactions and trading operations. We do not guarantee the accuracy and relevance of the information, and do not accept any responsibility for the possible loss of your money in connection with its use. We cannot guarantee the absolute accuracy of the displayed exchange rates. You must always confirm the exchange rate before making any transactions that may be affected by a change in the exchange rate.

### **Calendar.**

Time may not coincide. Also, we do not guarantee that this event will occur. The event can last more than 1 day. We enter into the calendar the day the event starts. (Event may start earlier or later. This will not be changed in the calendar.)

### **News and terms.**

We do not guarantee that the news and term can be accurate as stated in the official source. If necessary, we will provide a link to the source in news and terms.

### **Translation.**

In some cases, the translation of pages is made incorrectly, please, in case of misunderstanding, use the online translator. We are working on this problem.

### **Bonus Dogecoin.**

We do the Dogecoin coin distribution, after pressing the button, the coins are sent to FaucetHub. You can see the terms of use and privacy policy on the website FaucetHub: https://faucethub.io/privacy

### **Google Form.**

You can view Google’s policies here: policies.google.com/terms?gl=US&hl=en

When transmitting data to us in Google Forms, we do not collect your email addresses. In the settings, this feature is disabled.

### **Random.**

I’m Lucky – random/generator this is not Instructions and not recommendations. We are not responsible for any loss of your funds. Everything you do, you do at your own risk, be careful!

### **Ad units.**

We use ads from Google AdSense and Yandex Direct.

### **Updating or correcting the privacy policy.**

Last updated privacy policy was 27.05.19. If we update or correct this privacy policy, we will post those changes here.
